Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Verso: A treacherous crevasse in Victoria Glacier, Mt. Lefroy and Mt. Victoria in distance, Canadian Rockies, Canada: On the Canadian Pacific Railway, about 100 miles west of Calgary, is the Rocky Mountain Park of Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22-verso (Box 1606)
  - Among the jagged ice peaks of the Illecillewaet Glacier, British Columbia, Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Among the jagged ice peaks of the Illecillewaet Glacier, British Columbia, Canada: The fractured and fisured surface stands out more plainly because the human figure in the foreground, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23-verso (Box 1606)
  - The eccentric growth of cacao pods, Dominiea, British West Indies, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The eccentric growth of cacao pods, Dominiea, British West Indies: The cacao tree is a native of America and it was Christopher Columbus who first introduced its products to Europe, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24-verso (Box 1606)
  - Luxuriant tropical verdure along the canal, Fort de France Martinique, F.W.I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Luxuriant tropical verdure along the canal, Fort de France Martinique, F.W.I.: Martinique, one of the French islands of the Lesser Antilles, lies halfway between the British islands of Dominica and Saint Lucia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25-verso (Box 1606)
  - Old-fashioned sugar mill driven by the wind, Barbadoes, B.W.I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Old-fashioned sugar mill driven by the wind, Barbadoes, B.W.I.: The island of Barbadoes is the most easterly of the Caribbees, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26-verso (Box 1606)
  - Soufriere's Mammoth Crater - Volcanic Terror of St. Vincet, B.W.I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Soufriere's Mammoth Crater - Volcanic Terror of St. Vincet, B.W.I.: For two years previous to 1812 the inhabitants of the West Indies and the coast of South America had been terrified by earthquake shocks, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27-verso (Box 1606)
  - Farming scene, province of Havana, Cuba, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Farming scene, province of Havana, Cuba: Here is a typical rural scene in Cuba, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28-verso (Box 1606)
  - Cutting tobacco - a typical plantation scene near Havana, Cuba, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Cutting tobacco - a typical plantation scene near Havana, Cuba: This is a glimpse into the best tobacco-growing country in the world, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29-verso (Box 1606)
  - Carding room, cotton mills, Orizaba, Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Carding room, cotton mills, Orizaba, Mexico: Orizaba is a thriving, industrial city 70 miles sothwest of Vera Cruz, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30-verso (Box 1606)
  - Highly decorated interior of the Church of San Francisco, Puebla, Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Highly decorated interior of the Church of San Francisco, Puebla, Mexico: Because of the number and grandeur of its churches, its many covenants, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31-verso (Box 1606)
  - Ixtaccihuatl (The White Woman), 16,900 ft., seen from the Sacred Mount, Amecameca, Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Ixtaccihuatl (The White Woman), 16,900 ft., seen from the Sacred Mount, Amecameca, Mexico: We are stnading upon Sacre Monte (The Sacred Mount), an enormous pyramid of earth built centuries ago, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32-verso (Box 1606)
  - Gathering the luscious fruit of a heavily laden mango tree, Cuernavaca, Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Gathering the luscious fruit of a heavily laden mango tree, Cuernavaca, Mexico: This prolific mango tree is growing in Cuernavaca, a charming town in Mexico, fifty miles from Mexico City, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33-verso (Box 1606)
  - Filling pig skins with juice from Maguey plant used in making Pulque, the native drink, Tacuba, Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Filling pig skins with juice from Maguey plant used in making Pulque, the native drink, Tacuba, Mexico: in different parts of the world men make drinks from the juices of various plants, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34-verso (Box 1606)
  - Plaza and church of Santo Domingo, City of Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Plaza and church of Santo Domingo, City of Mexico: This church is all that now remains of a one-time great monastery established in Mexico City in 1526 by an order founded several centuries earlier in Old Spain \, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35-verso (Box 1606)
  - Hat market, City of Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Hat market, City of Mexico: In Mexico men wear hats like the ones you see in this city market, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36-verso (Box 1606)
  - Pyramid of the Sun, from Pyramid of the Moon, San Juan Teotihuacan, Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Pyramid of the Sun, from Pyramid of the Moon, San Juan Teotihuacan, Mexico: The Pyramid of the Sun and Moon are twenty-seven miles northeast of the City of Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37-verso (Box 1606)
  - The world's greatest silver mining city, Guanajuato, Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The world's greatest silver mining city, Guanajuato, Mexico: Guanajuato is the name of a city and also of a state in the Republic of Mexico, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38-verso (Box 1606)
  - National Theater in Guatemala City, Guatemala, Central America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: National Theater in Guatemala City, Guatemala, Central America: This theater is one of the best in Central America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39-verso (Box 1606)
  - Escuintla and the Twin Volcanoes, Fuego and Acatenango, Guatemala, C.A., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Escuintla and the Twin Volcanoes, Fuego and Acatenango, Guatemala, C.A.: Guatemala is the northern-most of the Central American countries, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40-verso (Box 1606)
  - Tortilla making, Salvador, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Tortilla making, Salvador: Salvador is about the size of New Jersey, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41-verso (Box 1606)
  - Sunday in the market Amapola, Honduras, Central America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Sunday in the market Amapola, Honduras, Central America: Honduras, a republic in Central America, covers an area of about forty-five thousand square miles, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42-verso (Box 1606)
  - The historic cathedral of Leon, Micaragua, Central America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The historic cathedral of Leon, Micaragua, Central America: Leon is the capital city of the department of the same name, and the largest city of the republic, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43-verso (Box 1606)
  - In the heart of Old Heredia, Costa Rica, C.A., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: In the heart of Old Heredia, Costa Rica, C.A.: This team looks odd to eyes accustomed to automobiles, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44-verso (Box 1606)
  - Harvesting Bananas, Costa Rica, Central America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Harvesting Bananas, Costa Rica, Central America: As we look at this luxuriant plantation we get the feeling of actually breathing the hot and humid atmosphere of a tropical jungle, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45-verso (Box 1606)
  - Rubber tree, showing scars from cutting and other tropical vegetation, Panama, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Rubber tree, showing scars from cutting and other tropical vegetation, Panama: The rubber tree is the small one in the center of the view, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46-verso (Box 1606)
  - Busy scene on the Panama Canal - looking south over Gatun Locks and Gatun Lake Emergency Dam in position Panama is a sort of multiple personality; it is at once a country, city, isthmus, bay and canal, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Busy scene on the Panama Canal - looking south over Gatun Locks and Gatun Lake Emergency Dam in position Panama is a sort of multiple personality; it is at once a country, city, isthmus, bay and canal, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47-verso (Box 1606)
  - Water carriers and thatched-roof homes, Barranquilla, Colombia, South America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Water carriers and thatched-roof homes, Barranquilla, Colombia, South America: We are in the quaint Colombian city of Baranquilla, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48-verso (Box 1606)
  - How the equatorial sun goes down in glory - outlook from Floating Inn, Babahoyo, Ecuador, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: How the equatorial sun goes down in glory - outlook from Floating Inn, Babahoyo, Ecuador: The placid river below us, pursuing its winding way to the Pacific Ocean nearly 75 miles away, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49-verso (Box 1606)
  - Quito, Capital of Ecuado and center of the equatorial Andes, looking W. 50 miles towards the distant Pacific, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Quito, Capital of Ecuado and center of the equatorial Andes, looking W. 50 miles towards the distant Pacific: We are three miles from the city and one mile from that little bridge down in the valley, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50-verso (Box 1606)
  - Sumptuous wall decorations of gold in an aisle of the Church of La Compania, Quito, Ecuador, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Sumptuous wall decorations of gold in an aisle of the Church of La Compania, Quito, Ecuador: Quito, the city of which this sumptuous church is one of the chief ornaments, lies at so great an elevation, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51-verso (Box 1606)
  - Homes on stilts where the families of laborers live - cacao plantation, La Clementina, Ecuador, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Homes on stilts where the families of laborers live - cacao plantation, La Clementina, Ecuador: Ecuador has a most unique geographical position astride the equator, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52-verso (Box 1606)
  - Lima, Peru, from hill N.E. of city, Rimac River, twin-towered cathedral, Bull Ring, shops and homes, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Lima, Peru, from hill N.E. of city, Rimac River, twin-towered cathedral, Bull Ring, shops and homes: We are looking over the quaintest city of the western hemisphere, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53-verso (Box 1606)
  - Planting sugar cane in a large hacienda near Lima, Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Planting sugar cane in a large hacienda near Lima, Peru: After the fields are plowed and harrowed, the next task on the sugar hacienda is to set out the cane, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54-verso (Box 1606)
  - Llamas, S. American cousins of the camel, resting between journeys, Cerro de Pasco, Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Llamas, S. American cousins of the camel, resting between journeys, Cerro de Pasco, Peru: Cerro de Pasco is built over a silver mine and there are hundreds of silver and copper mines the mountains around it, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55-verso (Box 1606)
  - Refining silver in smelter at the famous mining center of Cerro de Pasco, Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Refining silver in smelter at the famous mining center of Cerro de Pasco, Peru: Cerro de Pasco is a mining town in the highlands of Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56-verso (Box 1606)
  - Selling potatoes in their native land - market before the Jesuit Church and College, Cuzco, Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Selling potatoes in their native land - market before the Jesuit Church and College, Cuzco, Peru: In spite of the name given them, Irish potatoes first came from Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57-verso (Box 1606)
  - Threatening majesty of El Misti (20,012ft.), a famous volcano seen from Arequipa, Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Threatening majesty of El Misti (20,012ft.), a famous volcano seen from Arequipa, Peru: We are near the old Spanish bridge over the Rio Chili, in the western part of Arequipa, in southern Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58-verso (Box 1606)
  - In the heart of the awesome Andes - peering from Oroya Railroad into Rimac River Gorge, Peru, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: In the heart of the awesome Andes - peering from Oroya Railroad into Rimac River Gorge, Peru: There were many almost unsurmountable difficulties to be overcome when that railroad below was built, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59-verso (Box 1606)
  - Calle de Sacarnaca, with native shops and picturesque patrons, La Paz, Bolivia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Calle de Sacarnaca, with native shops and picturesque patrons, La Paz, Bolivia: Here we have a panorama of Bolivian native life, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60-verso (Box 1606)
  - Lake Titicaca, largest of South American lakes, 12,645 feet above the sea, and Mount Sorata, Bolivia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Lake Titicaca, largest of South American lakes, 12,645 feet above the sea, and Mount Sorata, Bolivia: The great body of water across which we are looking from the steamer's deck, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61-verso (Box 1606)
  - Nitrate for agriculture and for war being sacked for shipment, Chile, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Nitrate for agriculture and for war being sacked for shipment, Chile: Nitrate is an important chemical fertilizer, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62-verso (Box 1606)
  - Ox teams and drivers in rural Chile, "The Ribbon Republic" along west coast of South America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Ox teams and drivers in rural Chile, "The Ribbon Republic" along west coast of South America: The whole of Chile is mountainous and subject to to frequent and violent earrthquakes, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63-verso (Box 1606)
  - The bay and city, Valaparaiso, Chile, S. Am., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The bay and city, Valaparaiso, Chile, S. Am.: The word "Valparaiso" means "valley of paradise", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64-verso (Box 1606)
  - Indians on the straits of Magellan near Punta Arenas, Chile, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Indians on the straits of Magellan near Punta Arenas, Chile: On the straits of Magellan is located the city of Punta Arenas, the farthest southern city in the world, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65-verso (Box 1606)
  - Inca Lake, nestling in the heart of the Andes, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Inca Lake, nestling in the heart of the Andes: You are standing on the roof of the Americas, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66-verso (Box 1606)
  - The most costly docks in the western hemispehere, Buenos Aires, Argentina, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The most costly docks in the western hemispehere, Buenos Aires, Argentina: Buenos Aires is to South America what New York is to the north - the principal gateway to a continent, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67-verso (Box 1606)
  - Argentina's famous shorthorn cattle on range. La Plata, Argentina, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Argentina's famous shorthorn cattle on range. La Plata, Argentina: This fine herd of cattle is on a ranch near the city of La Plata, a few miles southeast of Buenos Aires, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68-verso (Box 1606)
  - One of the mightiest of cataracts - Iguazu Falls, Argentina, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: One of the mightiest of cataracts - Iguazu Falls, Argentina: We are in northern Argentina on the border line of Brazil, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69-verso (Box 1606)
  - Independence Plaza, Montevideo, Uruguay, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Independence Plaza, Montevideo, Uruguay: Uruguay is the smallest country in South America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70-verso (Box 1606)
  - The Municipal Theater. One of the handsomest playhouses in the world. Sao Paulo, Brazil, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The Municipal Theater. One of the handsomest playhouses in the world. Sao Paulo, Brazil: Sao Paulo is a city of more than half a million inhabitants, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71-verso (Box 1606)
  - Rio de janeiro, the Metropolis of Brazil, S.E. toward Sugarloaf Mountain and the Bay, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Rio de janeiro, the Metropolis of Brazil, S.E. toward Sugarloaf Mountain and the Bay: We are standing on a hilltop between the mountains and a placid arm of the bay, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72-verso (Box 1606)
  - Palm-fringed Rua Viscounte de Itauna, and Mangue Canal, Rio de Janeiro Brazil, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Palm-fringed Rua Viscounte de Itauna, and Mangue Canal, Rio de Janeiro Brazil: The Mangue Canal occupies the center of a splendid double thoroughfare in Rio de Janeiro, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73-verso (Box 1606)
  - Lower City and Harbor, Bahia, Brazil, S.A., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Lower City and Harbor, Bahia, Brazil, S.A.: Which way is Bahia from Rio de Janeiro? In which direction is it from the equator?..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74-verso (Box 1606)
  - Overlooking Caracas, the capital of Venezuela, "The Land Where it is Always Summer", circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Overlooking Caracas, the capital of Venezuela, "The Land Where it is Always Summer": Caracas is not only the capital, but also the commercial center of Venezuela, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75-verso (Box 1606)
  - In the market place, Caracas, Venezuela, South America, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: In the market place, Caracas, Venezuela, South America: Here we can observe Venezuelan types, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76-verso (Box 1606)
  - The narrow streets of La Guayra, Venezuela - native method of distributing milk unadulterated, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The narrow streets of La Guayra, Venezuela - native method of distributing milk unadulterated: La Guayra is the port of the city of Caracas, the capital of Venezuela, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77-verso (Box 1606)
  - Blarney Castle, near Cork, Ireland, famous as traditional shrine of Irish wit, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Blarney Castle, near Cork, Ireland, famous as traditional shrine of Irish wit: Who has not heard of the Blarney Stone?..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78-verso (Box 1606)
  - The Thursday live stock market in High St., Killarney, Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The Thursday live stock market in High St., Killarney, Ireland: Once a week, on thursdays, the farmers from the surrounding country bring to this particular street, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79-verso (Box 1606)
  - Lower Lake Killarney, Southwest from Lord Kenmare's Mansion County Kerry, Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Lower Lake Killarney, Southwest from Lord Kenmare's Mansion County Kerry, Ireland: We are looking from the mansion of Lord Kenmare, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80-verso (Box 1606)
  - Historic Ross Castle and the famous Irish jaunting Car, Lakes of Killarney, Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Historic Ross Castle and the famous Irish jaunting Car, Lakes of Killarney, Ireland: Ross Castle is a fortress of the 14th century, now in graceful ruins, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81-verso (Box 1606)
  - The picturesque home of a prosperous farmer in County Kerry, Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The picturesque home of a prosperous farmer in County Kerry, Ireland: We are in the southwest corner of Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82-verso (Box 1606)
  - The O'Connell Monument and the Nelson Pillar, O'Connell Street, Dublin, Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The O'Connell Monument and the Nelson Pillar, O'Connell Street, Dublin, Ireland: Two monuments adorn this broad and beautiful avenue, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83-verso (Box 1606)
  - Cutting peat in Northwest Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Cutting peat in Northwest Ireland: Ireland has little coal, no wood for fuel, as the forest have been cut down long ago, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84-verso (Box 1606)
  - Some of the 40,000 columns of the Famous Giant's Causeway on the coast of Northern Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Some of the 40,000 columns of the Famous Giant's Causeway on the coast of Northern Ireland: For nearly fourmiles along this shore the rocks are more or less like these, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85-verso (Box 1606)
  - Royal Avenue from Donegal Place, most important street of Belfast, Ireland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Royal Avenue from Donegal Place, most important street of Belfast, Ireland: This is Belfast, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86-verso (Box 1606)
  - Overlooking the beautiful valley of the Tay, Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Overlooking the beautiful valley of the Tay, Scotland: The Tay is the largest river in Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87-verso (Box 1606)
  - "The Spot an Angel Deigned to Grace" - Loch Katrine, Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: "The Spot an Angel Deigned to Grace" - Loch Katrine, Scotland: The vista of wild and lovely lake and mountainside which here lies before us, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88-verso (Box 1606)
  - Stirling Castle, Seat of Old-time Kings, seen from ancient tilting-ground below, Stirling, Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Stirling Castle, Seat of Old-time Kings, seen from ancient tilting-ground below, Stirling, Scotland: This seat of old-time kings is one of the most interesting and historic piles in old Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89-verso (Box 1606)
  - Outlook northeast from Castle, scene of heroic struggles to the Wallace Monument, Stirling, Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: Outlook northeast from Castle, scene of heroic struggles to the Wallace Monument, Stirling, Scotland: We are facing towards Pert, some thirty miles away, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90-verso (Box 1606)
  - The Old Forth Bridge, Stirling, Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The Old Forth Bridge, Stirling, Scotland: Six hundred years ago the Forth River and the near by country was the scene of one of the famous conflicts in Scottish history, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91-verso (Box 1606)
  - "We'll take a cup o' kindness yet for auld lange syne" - a Highland Home, Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: "We'll take a cup o' kindness yet for auld lange syne" - a Highland Home, Scotland: There are even yet people in the Highlands who speak and understand nothing but Gaelic, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92-verso (Box 1606)
  - The Forth Bridge, the pride of Scotland, from the deck of an American battleship near Edinburgh, Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: The Forth Bridge, the pride of Scotland, from the deck of an American battleship near Edinburgh, Scotland: Swinging in vast meshes like gigantic spider webs, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93-verso (Box 1606)
  - National Gallery, Scott Monument and Princes Street, from Castle, Edinburgh Scotland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94 (Box 1606)
  - Verso: National Gallery, Scott Monument and Princes Street, from Castle, Edinburgh Scotland: The Old Town is down at our right, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94-verso (Box 1606)